{ "question": "vôo", "wrong_answer_1":'seat', "right_answer":'flight', "wrong_answer_2":'gate'}
{ "question": "embarque", "wrong_answer_1":'meal', "right_answer":'boarding', "wrong_answer_2":'flight attendant'}
{ "question": "cartão de embarque", "wrong_answer_1":'flight attendant', "right_answer":'boarding pass', "wrong_answer_2":'confirmation code'}
{ "question": "portão de embarque", "wrong_answer_1":'time', "right_answer":'gate', "wrong_answer_2":'meal'}
{ "question": "refeição", "wrong_answer_1":'restroom', "right_answer":'meal', "wrong_answer_2":'drink'}
{ "question": "banheiro", "wrong_answer_1":'luggage', "right_answer":'restroom', "wrong_answer_2":'door'}
{ "question": "prioridade", "wrong_answer_1":'confirmation code', "right_answer":'priority', "wrong_answer_2":'land'}
{ "question": "código de reserva", "wrong_answer_1":'departure', "right_answer":'confimation code', "wrong_answer_2":'check in luggage'}
{ "question": "identidade", "wrong_answer_1":'balcão', "right_answer":'id', "wrong_answer_2":'bagagem'}
{ "question": "assento", "wrong_answer_1":'card', "right_answer":'seat', "wrong_answer_2":'meal'}


    
      